<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Branchis</title><description>Divulgación científica</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.11</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 08:15:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>About us</title><description>&lt;h5 id="martabroto"&gt;Marta Broto&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/05/WP_20160530_16_45_05_Pro.jpg" alt="Marta Broto" align="right" style="width: 200px; left: 15%;"&gt;  
Marta Broto holds a MSc degree in Organic Chemistry from the University of Barcelona and is currently finishing her PhD at &lt;b&gt;IQAC-CSIC&lt;/b&gt;. Her research focuses on the development of multiplexed and multimodal diagnostic platforms based on specifically functionalized particles.

&lt;br&gt;  
&lt;br&gt;

During her pre-doctoral training period, she spent a 4-month&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/untit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7083d4ac-607e-42fb-baf8-1af7445741a6</guid><dc:creator>Diego de Fabregas Ugalde</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 06:38:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h5 id="martabroto"&gt;Marta Broto&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/05/WP_20160530_16_45_05_Pro.jpg" alt="Marta Broto" align="right" style="width: 200px; left: 15%;"&gt;  
Marta Broto holds a MSc degree in Organic Chemistry from the University of Barcelona and is currently finishing her PhD at &lt;b&gt;IQAC-CSIC&lt;/b&gt;. Her research focuses on the development of multiplexed and multimodal diagnostic platforms based on specifically functionalized particles.

&lt;br&gt;  
&lt;br&gt;

During her pre-doctoral training period, she spent a 4-month internship in the Chemical Engineering department of University of California Santa Barbara focusing on drug delivery particles. She has experience in science communication as a member of &lt;b&gt;Scientists Dating Forum&lt;/b&gt; and cofounder of &lt;b&gt;Branchis&lt;/b&gt;.

&lt;br&gt;  
&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Marta Broto tiene un máster en Química Orgánica de la Universidad de Barcelona y, actualmente, está terminando su tesis doctoral en el &lt;b&gt;IQAC-CSIC&lt;/b&gt;. Su investigación se centra en el desarrollo de plataformas de diagnóstico multiplexadas y multimodales basados en partículas con funcionalizaciones específicas.&lt;/i&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;i&gt;Durante su etapa predoctoral, hizo una estancia de 4 meses en el departamento de Ingeniería Química de la Universidad de California Santa Bárbara, centrándose en partículas para la liberación de fármacos. Sra. Broto tienen experiencia en comunicación científica como miembro del &lt;b&gt;Scientists Dating Forum&lt;/b&gt; y cofundadora de &lt;b&gt;Branchis&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h5 id="anasanchis"&gt;Ana Sanchis&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2017/05/Captura.PNG" alt="Ana Sanchis" align="right" style="width: 200px; left: 15%;"&gt;  
Ana Sanchis holds a degree in Biotechnology from the Autonomous University of Barcelona, with a MSc degree in Advanced Immunology from the University of Barcelona. She is currently finishing her PhD at &lt;b&gt;IQAC-CSIC&lt;/b&gt;, focusing her research on the development of multiplexed platforms for the detection of environmental pollutants, as well as the exploration of new assay surfaces such as nanoparticles and flexible polymers.  
&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
During her pre-doctoral training period, she became interested in the world of business and entrepreneurship, and today she has experience in scientific communication as a member of &lt;b&gt;Scientists Dating Forum&lt;/b&gt; and cofounder of &lt;b&gt;Branchis&lt;/b&gt;.  
&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;i&gt;Ana Sanchis es licenciada en Biotecnología por la Universidad Autónoma de Barcelona, con un máster en Inmunología avanzada por la Universidad de Barcelona. Actualmente está finalizando su tesis doctoral en el &lt;b&gt;IQAC-CSIC&lt;/b&gt;, centrando su investigación en el desarrollo de plataformas multiplexadas de detección de contaminantes medioambientales, así como en la exploración de nuevas superficies de ensayo como lo son nanopartículas y polímeros flexibles.&lt;/i&gt;  
&lt;/p&gt;  

&lt;p align="justify"&gt;  
&lt;i&gt;Durante su etapa predoctoral, despertó su interés en el mundo de la empresa y el emprendimiento, y a día de hoy cuenta con experiencia en comunicación científica como miembro del &lt;b&gt;Scientists Dating Forum&lt;/b&gt; y cofundadora de &lt;b&gt;Branchis&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Welcome to Ghost</title><description>&lt;p&gt;You're live! Nice. We've put together a little post to introduce you to the Ghost editor and get you started. You can manage your content by signing in to the admin area at &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;your blog URL&amp;gt;/ghost/&lt;/code&gt;. When you arrive, you can select this post from a list&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/welcome-to-ghost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">289d7d78-6e96-4bf9-8432-2a1e08d7e4b2</guid><category>Getting Started</category><dc:creator>Diego de Fabregas Ugalde</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 07:43:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You're live! Nice. We've put together a little post to introduce you to the Ghost editor and get you started. You can manage your content by signing in to the admin area at &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;your blog URL&amp;gt;/ghost/&lt;/code&gt;. When you arrive, you can select this post from a list on the left and see a preview of it on the right. Click the little pencil icon at the top of the preview to edit this post and read the next section!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="gettingstarted"&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ghost uses something called Markdown for writing. Essentially, it's a shorthand way to manage your post formatting as you write!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing in Markdown is really easy. In the left hand panel of Ghost, you simply write as you normally would. Where appropriate, you can use &lt;em&gt;shortcuts&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;style&lt;/strong&gt; your content. For example, a list:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item number two
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A nested item&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A final item&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or with numbers!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember to buy some milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drink the milk  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tweet that I remembered to buy the milk, and drank it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id="links"&gt;Links&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to link to a source? No problem. If you paste in a URL, like &lt;a href="http://ghost.org"&gt;http://ghost.org&lt;/a&gt; - it'll automatically be linked up. But if you want to customise your anchor text, you can do that too! Here's a link to &lt;a href="http://ghost.org"&gt;the Ghost website&lt;/a&gt;. Neat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="whataboutimages"&gt;What about Images?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Images work too! Already know the URL of the image you want to include in your article? Simply paste it in like this to make it show up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://ghost.org/images/ghost.png" alt="The Ghost Logo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure which image you want to use yet? That's ok too. Leave yourself a descriptive placeholder and keep writing. Come back later and drag and drop the image in to upload:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="quoting"&gt;Quoting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a link isn't enough, you want to quote someone on what they've said. Perhaps you've started using a new blogging platform and feel the sudden urge to share their slogan? A quote might be just the way to do it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Ghost - Just a blogging platform&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id="workingwithcode"&gt;Working with Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got a streak of geek? We've got you covered there, too. You can write inline &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; blocks really easily with back ticks. Want to show off something more comprehensive? 4 spaces of indentation gets you there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;.awesome-thing {
    display: block;
    width: 100%;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="readyforabreak"&gt;Ready for a Break?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw 3 or more dashes down on any new line and you've got yourself a fancy new divider. Aw yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;h3 id="advancedusage"&gt;Advanced Usage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There's one fantastic secret about Markdown. If you want, you can write plain old HTML and it'll still work! Very flexible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="text" placeholder="I'm an input field!"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That should be enough to get you started. Have fun - and let us know what you think :)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>